<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Write-Ups on GazooArmy</title>
    <link>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Write-Ups on GazooArmy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:22:12 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CTF2 - ForensicChall1</title>
      <link>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/ctf2/chall1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:22:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/ctf2/chall1/</guid>
      <description>binary static analysis   File analysis
$ file collabin   Test
 test test    Test ok
 test    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB Apocalypse 2023 - Forensic Challs</title>
      <link>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/apocalypse2023/forensicchalls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:22:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/apocalypse2023/forensicchalls/</guid>
      <description>Plaintext Tleasure Threat intelligence has found that the aliens operate through a command and control server hosted on their infrastructure. Pandora managed to penetrate their defenses and have access to their internal network. Because their server uses HTTP, Pandora captured the network traffic to steal the server&amp;rsquo;s administrator credentials. Open the provided file using Wireshark, and locate the username and password of the admin.
Alien Cradle In an attempt for the aliens to find more information about the relic, they launched an attack targeting Pandora&amp;rsquo;s close friends and partners that may know any secret information about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB Apocalypse 2023 - Packet Cyclone</title>
      <link>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/apocalypse2023/forensics_packet_cyclone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:22:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/apocalypse2023/forensics_packet_cyclone/</guid>
      <description>download file
Pandora&amp;rsquo;s friend and partner, Wade, is the one that leads the investigation into the relic&amp;rsquo;s location. Recently, he noticed some weird traffic coming from his host. That led him to believe that his host was compromised. After a quick investigation, his fear was confirmed. Pandora tries now to see if the attacker caused the suspicious traffic during the exfiltration phase. Pandora believes that the malicious actor used rclone to exfiltrate Wade&amp;rsquo;s research to the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB Apocalypse 2023 - ReverseChall1</title>
      <link>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/apocalypse2023/reversingchall1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:22:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/apocalypse2023/reversingchall1/</guid>
      <description>binary static analysis  File analysis $ file bin  Test  test test    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB Apocalypse 2023 - Reversing Challs</title>
      <link>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/apocalypse2023/reversingchalls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:22:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/apocalypse2023/reversingchalls/</guid>
      <description>Shattered Tablet 325 very easy She Shells C Shells 350 very easy Needle in a Haystack 325 very easy Hunting License 350 easy Cave System 375 easy Alien Saboteaur 425 medium Gimmick DSP 825 medium Vessel Cartographer 1000 hard Somewhat Linear 425 hard Analogue Signal Processing 825 insane  Shattered Tablet Deep in an ancient tomb, you&amp;rsquo;ve discovered a stone tablet with secret information on the locations of other relics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTB Apocalypse 2023 - Roten</title>
      <link>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/apocalypse2023/forensics_roten/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:22:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://goozyhtb.github.io/CTFwriteups/post/apocalypse2023/forensics_roten/</guid>
      <description>Roten The iMoS is responsible for collecting and analyzing targeting data across various galaxies. The data is collected through their webserver, which is accessible to authorized personnel only. However, the iMoS suspects that their webserver has been compromised, and they are unable to locate the source of the breach. They suspect that some kind of shell has been uploaded, but they are unable to find it. The iMoS have provided you with some network data to analyse, its up to you to save us.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
